Structure, style, story:
what goes where?
	“When someone’s new to WP, they don’t know everything you can DO with WP.” - Karen M, WordPress 101
		Designers and devs too.
		Imbalances:
			content hard-coded in php file
				Wasted time
				Content doesn’t make it into the database.
			CSS crimes
				showing/hiding stuff instead of unregistering it
					display: none;
					!important;
					overflow: hidden;
			inline styles: presentation versus communication
				I hate <span> worse tha mayo and sour cream.
				I’m not talking about email. Whole different story.
	Anatomy of a WP site
		1. Structure
			Files
				Frameworks and APIs:
					Backbone, Node, Angular, Grunt, Gulp …
					Sounds like a wedding scene in Game of Thrones.
				PHP
					Outputs layouts with HTML
					Does stuff an app might.
					Plays with the database.
			Information structure
				Everything starts as a post.
					Article
					Video
					Episode
					Product
					Photo spread
					Property listing
				Pages are collections of posts.
					Pages we make
						News/magazine sections
						Store layouts: catalogue pages
					Archives combine themselves, naturally.
						Category
						Author
						Post type
						Date
				“But all the cool layout stuff happens in page templates …”
					Which artfully arrange our post excerpts.
					Want cool stuff on posts?
						Body classes
						CPT
		2. Style
			Files
				CSS
				jQuery
			To us, this is the priority.
				It’s also the fun part.
				Once they trust us, we get to make Rules about the Brand.
				It’s how we sell ourselves (portfolio)
					Seriously. What shoe store is gonna look at your code?
					“I dunno if you’re the right firm for us. You don’t concatenate your JavaScript.”
				And how they’ll sell themselves
					dog-whistle branding
						Attract your target
						Repel the others
					Stanford study on web cred: BJ Fogg
		3. Story
			For us, it’s this afterthought we call content.  That weird stuff we drop in at the end, after the fun’s over.
				We don’t even understand a site owner’s passion for the subject.
				Ferman: “Well, what would YOU do if YOUR whole life was cat food?”
			For them, the story IS the site.
				It’s their business.
				Or their life.
			Files:
				Damn near anything.
					Text
					Visuals
					Audio
					Video
					Real-time
						Chat
						Streams
	Case in point: Tennis Machines.
		Live site
			Reveries
				Foundation 4
				Page templates w/ ACF.
				Hard-coded home page
			Plugins for caching, seo, other functionality
		Current mods
			WooCommerce
			Two widgets on home page
			Vid footage in the can, needs cutting
			New material is posts, not pages.
		Goals:
			From ACF rows on a page to separate posts/products on a page.
			Fully widgetized home page
				SEO: home pages need to change.
					Our new and improved Curator is now a custom WordPress plugin—and it’s artificially intelligent! … This means our homepage and section landing pages are constantly changing with new stories all day long. - the Wired relaunch
				Workflow: If clients want to add stuff, they can add posts.
			Genesis
				Genesis SEO
				Hooks
				My Foundation child theme
				I like the Genesis Featured Posts widget
better than one I grabbed for an Underscores demo in Phoenix.
